<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Week II on Xtern Bootcamp 2018</title>
    <link>http://xtbc18s2.github.io/week2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Week II on Xtern Bootcamp 2018</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://xtbc18s2.github.io/week2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5: Intro to React</title>
      <link>http://xtbc18s2.github.io/week2/day5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xtbc18s2.github.io/week2/day5/</guid>
      <description>Monday, June 11, 2018
Lecture Videos Morning:
 Playlist | Day 5, Part 1  Afternoon:
 Playlist | Day 5, Part 1  Topics ES2015+ (ES6+)  Modules (import/export) - ES2015 modules on Babel  React  Imperative vs. Declarative Components  JSX - Docs: Introducing JSX Props - Docs: Components and Props State - Docs: State and Lifecycle   Examples React Basic App A basic React application requires a minimum of four things:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6: React</title>
      <link>http://xtbc18s2.github.io/week2/day6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xtbc18s2.github.io/week2/day6/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, June 12, 2018
Lecture Videos Morning:
 Playlist | Day 6, Part 1  Afternoon:
 Playlist | Day 6, Part 1  Topics React  create-react-app CSS in JS Lists and Keys Using map with components Stateless Functional Components  Stateless Functional Components in React Functional Components vs. Stateless Functional Components vs. Stateless Components Nine Wins You Might Have Overlooked  Controlled vs Uncontrolled Forms Controlled and uncontrolled form inputs in React don&amp;rsquo;t have to be complicated Property initializers (and arrow functions)  Examples React create-react-app  Documentation/README  Lists and Keys  Key props on list items  Using map with Components Person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7: React Components &amp; Firebase</title>
      <link>http://xtbc18s2.github.io/week2/day7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xtbc18s2.github.io/week2/day7/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday, June 13, 2018
Lecture Videos Morning:
 Playlist | Day 7, Part 1  Afternoon:
 Playlist | Day 7, Part 1  Topics React  Methods as props Conditional Rendering The Component Lifecycle If-Else in JSX  JavaScript  Destructuring assignment Spread operator Ternary operators  Firebase  Firebase  Examples React Methods as props Sometimes one component needs to update another component&amp;rsquo;s state. It can&amp;rsquo;t do that directly, but it can call a method from that other component if it&amp;rsquo;s available via a prop.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>